i've been working with a young couple
for about a year and they came in
and they were feeling very overwhelmed
and i could see it all over their body
language and
um they're just their generals the way
that seemed a little bit different than
the way i usually knew them to be
and as we got into the meeting and as i
did my discovery questions
they told me that they had both their
kids in daycare and this was putting a
lot of financial stress
on their month month-to-month budget and
they were concerned because they also
had a bunch of money
on their line of credit so they had a
large balance on their line of credit
and they were not able to save every
month because they had to
pay off that line of credit or at least
to pay the interest payment so they
really felt like they weren't getting
anywhere and they weren't moving forward
in the right direction and
time was kind of passing them by and
their net worth wasn't going up so they
had valid concerns
and it was great that they brought those
to me and we were able to sit down and
talk about them and i suggested actually
that they look at consolidating their
debt
and it worked out perfectly with sort of
when their mortgage was coming up for
renewal
um they went in a little bit earlier to
do that they engaged a mortgage broker
they were able to consolidate their debt
and it really freed up their cash flow
so now all of a sudden we were back on
track
um they were saving a little bit every
month instead of just
you know paying off interest and it was
you know a slight
little adjustment a sort of
reorganization if you will of what was
already going on
but it made a massive difference and it
was slightly outside of like the average
advice that maybe would come from a
financial advisor
but i remember they brought in a plant
next time they came they were both
smiling they're like
you've made the world of difference for
us they actually were even able to like
renovate their home a bit with the whole
refinancing that they did
and move in the right direction so i
think of them when i think of
great to super advice
you